http://www.eddyline.com/customer-service/privacy-policy/

Kayaks
Choose a kayak from one of the menus on the right.
Click the
icon to view a comparison chart.
Technology & Innovation
Throughout our 49 year history, Eddyline has been a leader of innovation in manufacturing and design technology. We continue this legacy with thermoformed Carbonlite 2000 Technology.
Information
Technology & Innovation
Features & Benefits
FAQs
Videos
The Birth of a Kayak
About Us
About Us
EDDYLINE KAYAKS – a manufacturer of premier touring kayaks since 1971 with Legendary Designs by Tom Derrer. Family owned, proudly handcrafted by American workers and supporting the local economy.
Company & History
About Eddyline
Our History
History of Kayaks
Videos
The Birth of a Kayak
Customer Support
Customer Service
It gives us great personal satisfaction to provide "real" service to you, our customers. Real service is not something that can be bought or measured with money, it requires sincerity and integrity. At Eddyline, we realize that by serving your needs we secure our future business.
Your Kayak
Register Your Kayak
Owner's Manual (PDF)
Care & Repair
Kayak Information
Discontinued Model Info
FAQs
Contact
Contact Us
Find a Dealer
Dealers
Eddyline Dealers
Flagship Dealers stock the majority of Eddyline models and have them regularly available to demo during the local paddling season.
Dealers
Find a Dealer Near You
Become a Dealer
Become an Authorized Dealer
Community
In Our Community
Take a look at our videos and follow us on social media!
Read More »
Eddyline in the News
News
Articles of Interest
Videos
Employment Opportunities
Employment Application
Job Listings
Social Media
Shop
Home » Customer Support » Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Updated as of July 13th, 2016.
Eddyline Kayaks, LLC (“We”) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this privacy policy. This privacy policy explains the types of information that may be collected from you when you visit our website (www.eddyline.com) and our practices for collecting, using, and sharing that information.
The short version: The personal information (like name, email address, mailing address, and phone number) we collect is provided by you voluntarily and is used to better serve you. We do not sell, rent, share, or otherwise use the information you provide to us in a manner inappropriate to the reason it was provided.
Collection, Use, and Sharing of Information
You may generally browse our website anonymously without providing any personal information. However, there are cases in which we may ask you for personal information. Non-personal information (like IP address) may be collected automatically while browsing the website. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will not share your personal information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request.
Voluntary Contact: When you voluntarily contact us with a question or comment, we ask you to provide contact information (like name and email address). This information is used to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us.
Kayak Registration: When you register your kayak, we ask you to provide contact information (like name, phone number, and mailing address). This information is used to contact you if there is ever an issue or concern with your kayak.
Orders: When you purchase a product from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number and billing address). This information is used for billing purposes and to fulfill your order. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.
Automatically Collected Information: See Google Analytics and Google Maps API under Cookies and Tracking.
Your Choices and Access to Information
You may update or correct your online account information by logging into your online store account and updating your information. You may also do any of the following at any time by contacting us using the information provided at the bottom of this policy:
See what information we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any information we have about you.
Have us delete any information we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your information.
Security
We take reasonable measures, including administrative, physical, and electronic safeguards to protect your information from loss, theft, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.
Links
Our website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and read the privacy statements of any other site that collects your information.
Cookies and Tracking
Google Analytics: The only cookies in use on our site are for Google Analytics. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit when they do so, and how long they stayed. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve our site. Google Analytics collects information anonymously and reports website trends without personally identifying individual visitors. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy. You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to our site by disabling cookies on your browser.
Google Maps API: Our Dealer Locator uses the Google Maps API to function. Google’s ability to access, use, and share any information collected by the Google Maps API is restricted by the Google Maps API Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy.
California Privacy Rights
California Civil Code §1798.83 permits our visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding their disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us using the information at the bottom of this privacy policy.
Children
We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age. If we learn that we have collected the personal information of a child under 13, we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible.
Changes to this Policy
We may update and revise this privacy policy from time to time. Please check this privacy policy regularly for any updates or revisions.
Contact Information
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.
Digital Catalog (PDF)
Your Kayak
Register Your Kayak
Owner's Manual (PDF)
Share this on your favorite social network.
Copyright © 2020 Eddyline Kayaks.
Home | Eddyline Kayaks | Technology | About Us | Customer Support | Community | Dealer Resources | Shop | Privacy Policy
×Close
Search the Website
What can we help you find?
Cancel
×Close
Send Us An Email
Please fill in the fields below and click the Submit button.
All fields are required.
Your Name
Your Email
Comments and/or Questions
Please leave this field empty.
Cancel
×Close
Product Issues & Repair
Please fill in the fields below and click the Submit button.
*Required fields.
Photo 3Please leave this field empty.
